mp3fiesta.com 2008-12-17

# Privacypolicy – MP3fiesta.com

#### Privacy Policy

By registering on MP3fiesta.com, you agree to follow all the rules and accept sole responsibility. If you disagree with any point of the Agreement you should not subscribe to MP3fiesta.com. Site Administration reserves the right to change registration procedure or service rendering way. 

**IP address**  
The particularity of Internet industry requires us to follow the statistics on Customers’ IP addresses. The information helps us to deliver a superior level of customer service. It enables us to provide you with services that are of the most interest for you. IP address collecting also helps us to identify and solve technical problems. MP3fiesta.com takes all necessary precautions to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction.

**Cookies**  
According to the common practice accepted in the Internet, MP3fiesta.com Administration uses cookies. It helps us to understand which parts of our site are the most popular and what services are mostly required. Cookies are not used to elicit any private information such as Client’s login or password. Disabling cookies may interrupt your access to some of the MP3fiesta.com resources. 

**Your personal information**  
Anytime you interact with MP3fiesta.com the site Administration get access to your personal data such as downloads, e-mail address, correspondence, statistics etc. Your personal information enables us to keep you posted about new releases and events that you might like to hear about. Your privacy is a priority at MP3fiesta.com and we do our best to protect it. The MP3fiesta.com Administration undertakes not to disclose any data without Client’s permission.

**Your financial information**  
Paying for the Site services, the Client has to notify the Administration of preferable payment method. provides all payments on MP3fiesta.com. To protect your personal information, the makes use of the SSL connection 3.0 (cryptographic protocol) on all the pages where input of personal information is required. The Site Administration is not informed about payment details. The Site Administration agrees to treat all other the financial data confidentially.
